I think I'll go see a movie. Kugisaki?
Too early to see a movie for me.
I think I'll go shopping.
You two have too much energy.
Well, I think I'll go home. See ya!
School is finally done.
You sure you don't want to see a movie?
My treat.
What are you going to see?
Human Earthworm 4. You're going alone!
I haven't even seen parts 1, 2, 3.
two or three I think you'd
be fine jumping in at four in
this movie the mad scientist
from human earthworm one dr.
Richter is making his long-awaited
reappearance in the hybrid
human earthworm fusion from the
doctors experiments is going
to give rise to an enhanced human
earthworm what the hell that's
so gross the poor human earthworm
who barely escaped from dr.
Richter with its life finally
wanders into a campground
where a group of college
students are and that's
when the real story kicks
off so one of the college
students is a kind woman
who's an animal rights
activist and the human
earthworm falls in love
with her who could ever
love me i'm no longer human
you're more human than
anyone else i know it's a
monster kill it kevin stop
don't if we kill him we're the
So it's actually a love story!
Yeah, I don't want to see some
worm-o-man doing anything.
He's a human earthworm.
Whatever, it doesn't matter. Have fun.
I'm going shopping for a while.
Want to come with me?
I just spent five minutes telling
you I'm going to the movies.
Okay. Later, then.
Special Grade is a rank reserved for those
sorcerers who display
exceptional abilities.
In my opinion,
First Grade is the true
rank for the sorcerers
who will lead other sorcerers
and jujutsu society.
They must stand above comparison to
semi-first grades in terms of peril,
secrecy, and salary.
Now with that in mind, what
are your recommendations?
Maki Zenin, Panda.
Megumi Fushiguro, Nobara Kugisaki, and of
course there's my brother, Yuji Itadori.
I will swear it on my name as Aoi Toto.
And on my name as Meimei.
I recommend those five
for first grade sorcerer.
Those who are recommended by at least two
first-grade sorcerers
must carry out missions,
all under the supervision
of an active first
-grade or first-grade equivalent sorcerer.
Then, if they are deemed fit, they will
be promoted to semi-first-grade sorcerer
and proceed to be assigned
first-grade missions on their own.
Following the results of those missions,
they either will or won't officially
become first-grade sorcerers.
My brother will accept the
recommendation to first class.
With Sukuna still uncooperative!
He'll need to go on a lot
more dangerous missions.
In order for him to raise the
chances of finding more fingers?
You understand what that means, don't you?
Ms.
May
What that means is it's going
to mean everything to them
Mr.
Toto
A bright future.
It means a bright future is
coming where the brothers
Aoi Toto and Yuji Itadori
face missions together.
A bright future lies ahead.
No.
You don't have to say it.
There's no guarantee I'll be the
one assigned to accompany you.
That's what you wanted to say.
But I'm quite certain this will happen.
It's as certain as ripe red
apples falling from a tree.
The two of us are drawn together.
Yes, it truly is.
Destiny!
No, I mean,
the sorcerers who
recommended him for first
class can't be assigned to accompany him.
Since we were the two first
class who recommended Itadori,
someone else will have to accompany
him on any of his upcoming missions.
Thanks for the game.
I have to be going now, Mr. Toto.
Um, excuse me
You were with Itadori
earlier, weren't you?
Come again?
You are my special
The way in the street, let's go
outside The way in the city of Tokyo,
the city of Tokyo The way in the street,
let's go outside I know you know what it's
wrong Let meal itI love you baby We say
prayers Let us all do
Hmmm Come through Each
I want to 10,000 What
issues Make
you die Your all
devil I make a soul Oh boy
You are my special Oh yeah,
my yeah, man No, I'm my world's
secure No, no, no, so we 죽.
We're all right
We're inside, make a song.
Your all devil.
That way I'm not. Oh boy!
You are my special.
We're special.
Welcome!
This is what I look like at our
middle school graduation ceremony.
Huh?
Seriously?
That was only six months ago!
What happened to you?
Well, yeah, I guess I've grown about
15 centimeters since graduation day.
Plus, I guess,
the combination of the stress of moving
to Tokyo and changing environments.
Whoa.
You're a real Kuroko City.
That's Itadori?
On graduation day, I worked up the courage
to ask if he'd take a photo with me.
Actually, what I wanted was
to ask for his phone number.
But I already knew that
we were moving to Tokyo.
So when I saw Itadori with you earlier,
I thought maybe with the
way I look now, I might...
Wait, Yuko, you mean that...
You mean it's like that, right?
Yes, that's what I mean, it's like that.
What's up, Ijichi?
Is Fushiguro still riding with you?
I just dropped you a location
pin to the restaurant I'm at.
Could you turn around and bring him here?
Thanks.
I'll see you soon.
Someone who knows Itadori pretty
well is on his way here right now.
Uh...
I think we should talk
to him about it first.
And you?
Hmm?
Well, if you're also interested
in Itadori, then... No.
If hell throws over and
dance the lombata...
Still no.
Hmm?
I just got the weirdest
feeling in my chest.
Did my heart skip a beat?
Okay, what's the big emergency?
Oh, hey there, Fushiguro.
Does Itadori have a girlfriend?
Huh?
This is Yuko Ozawa.
She knows Itadori from middle
school, if you know what I mean.
Oh, so it's like that, huh?
Yeah, totally like that.
He definitely doesn't have a girlfriend.
You sure?
When he had to transfer to Tokyo, he
didn't seem particularly upset about it.
He also has a pin-up
poster hanging in his room.
Anyone with a girlfriend wouldn't
have something like that hanging up,
because she would hate it.
Are you the type to
drink coffee black only
when women are around so you can show off?
So weird.
Did you call me here to ask me
about this or to ridicule me?
I always drink it black, so there.
By the way, do you happen
to know what his type is?
I think he might have mentioned
that he likes tall girls.
You have a real shot!
I'll text Izadori now.
Are you okay with that, Yuko?
Oh yeah.
That felt kinda curt.
Nah.
What the?
Fushiguro's here too?
That was fast
Oh... Crap.
What's that?
I didn't tell Isidori about Yuko.
So I traded in for prizes instead.
He definitely won't recognize
her after she changed so much.
Who are you?
That's the number one line you
don't want to hear when reuniting
with the guy from middle
school who you liked like that!
Isidori, this girl is - Wait a second.
This girl is - You're Ozawa.
What are you doing here? Mm-mm.
What a coincidence.
Okay, so, which girl in our
class do you like, Itadori?
I don't like any of them.
Yeah, but if you had to pick one.
Huh? Why?
Well, if I had to pick, I guess... Ozawa?
What?
No way, man, you're crazy!
She's fat!
Is she?
She's thoughtful and neat.
You can see it in the
way she eats and writes.
I think that's kind of cool.
I thought you said you like
tall girls with big butts.
That's its own thing.
You can't compare apples to oranges
or even lychee to dragon fruit.
It's easy for girls to get fat.
And when the human earth...
I started off as a fat cat.
Yeah, that was my favorite part, too.
He should totally make a
sequel where they bring Dr.
Richter back for Human Earthworm 2!
Aw, that'll be rad!
Hey, let's go see it again tonight!
But even I didn't have any interest in
choosing someone who wouldn't choose me.
Itadori saw a side of
me I wasn't aware of.
I hated all the boys,
except for him,
but I thought maybe with
the way I look now, I might,
maybe, but look at me, living by the
same standards as the people I hate.
Later.
Bye, guys.
See you later.
Can't tell how it went they could
have at least exchanged numbers.
I gave his cell number to her.
It should be okay
But more importantly, I've realized
my own feelings Fushiguro. Yeah,
the thought that Itadori
might land a girlfriend before
I'm able to get a boyfriend
really pisses me off to no end!
Is that so?
Sorry for the wait You need to walk
behind me. Huh? You're kidding.
What are you talking about here?
Huh? Oh?
Oh, thank you. Here. What?
Wait, what is this?
And while you're at it...
While I'm at what?
I know you're the type of gentleman
who'd feel bad making a lady carry them.
Sure.
Oh, crap!
The movie's starting!
Hey, let's go! Huh? Hey, hold on!
Don't get my stuff with you!
Come on!
There's no way I'm
watching some worm-o-man!
Fushiguro, you want some popcorn?
Caramel flavor, right?
Just don't tell me the plot
if we're gonna see worm-o-man.
I told you!
It's Human Earthworm 4!
They're only working
with curse users, though.
I want to leave the investigation
of Kyoto up to you, Urahime.
This way.
You've heard from Gojo about
the person leaking intel, right?
Yes, ma 'am.
There's probably two or more people
in contact with the curse users.
One would be a higher-up
well above the principle.
I won't be able to do
anything about that one.
The other would be someone passing
the information to that higher-up.
That's the one we're going to target.
They're only a suspect at this point,
so we'll capture and interrogate them.
So, who from Kyoto is it?
Huh?
That has to be the reason why they asked
those of us from Tokyo to come here.
Kugisaki, you're awesome.
The name of the mole is...
Mekumaru!
Oh, there you are.
Today is the last day for
you to turn in your notebook.
Makamaru?
Sorry, Miwa.
I'm going to sleep for a bit.
Please, take my notebook.
It's on my desk. Going to sleep?
It's still only the afternoon.
You really did go to sleep.
I wonder where the real
Makamaru actually is.
Mechamaru's actual body, Kokichi
Mode, is in the basement.
Now, it's not like he's suspicious.
It's more that everyone else wasn't.
So the process of elimination
leaves us with him.
Mechamaru's technique
is puppet manipulation.
Thanks to his heavenly pact, he can
manipulate puppets throughout all of Japan.
And if he has puppets we don't know about,
then it would be easy for him
to work as a mole if he wanted.
No way.
How can you miss a puppet
that size being a mole?
By using puppets the size
of a fly or mosquito.
Oh, yeah.
I didn't think of that.
In there.
They have arrived.
Wrong... Rune?
He knows that we're after him.
But on the other hand...
Now we're certain that
the mole is Mechamaru.
You're late.
I've been waiting.
I thought you forgot about me.
How could we forget about you?
You're personally familiar with
the terrifying nature of a pact.
You always smell so moldy.
I hate coming here.
And these are enemies.
Why don't we just kill him already?
No, we can't kill him yet, Mahito.
He agreed to cooperate with
us and provide information.
In exchange, we agreed to use your
idle transfiguration to fix his body.
That's the pact we all forged. Remember.
Killing him comes right after fixing him.
I wanted him to do some
work for us in Shibuya, too.
Such a shame.
You're the ones who broke
our pact first when you said
we won't lay a hand on the
people from the Kyoto School.
Konami's the one who did that.
Don't blame us for what somebody else did.
I won't argue with cursed spirits.
Fix me, scumbag. Hurry up.
Maybe I'll get carried away and
turn him into a caterpillar.
Mahito,
pacts that are forged with
others are very different
from the pacts that are
placed upon oneself.
The first aspect of a break is the
uncertain nature of the penalty.
If you break a pact with yourself,
whatever you were able
to gain in terms of the
improvement to your own
ability is lost forever?
But this time you can't break it,
because if you break this pact,
then we have no idea as to what kind
of disaster will eventually befall us.
Yeah, yeah.
You're actually lower than
a scumbag, so be grateful.
Idle Transfiguration.
You're no fun at all.
You should celebrate a bit more.
I'll do that after I'm
finished with my promise.
Hmm.
I suppose that's fair.
All right.
Shall we get started?
Want my help?
Don't you dare.
He's my toy now.
He escaped?
Well, it's not like we needed
to kill him as part of our pact.
It's pretty boring, though.
I wanted to have a match, not
go hunting for him, you know?
Now that's more like it, Puppet Master!
so you've been making something
like this in secret the whole time?
yes you had a reason to be a shut-in
after all he's inside it right?
he wouldn't want me to
touch him after all the
Cockpit, the seat of
his soul, is the head.
Expansion rate normal.
Perception feedback severed.
Someone lowered a veil.
Must be Code.
It's not just attempting
to trap me inside.
It's cutting off my signal.
This won't be as easy
as it was for Satoru.
That's right.
My victory condition is Satoru Gojo.
I have to use any means necessary
to get in contact with Satoru.
and tell him about the Shibuya plot.
Then I'll have him protect me.
But even if I want to focus on
Code, the one who lowered this veil,
Mahito is too dangerous to ignore.
I'll have to exorcise him first.
Go ahead.
Don't mind me at all.
I'm still at a disadvantage,
but I have a chance to win.
I've seen it all.
I have all the time I was bound.
All the cursed energy I
gained from that time.
I won't hold anything back.
Charge! One year!
Burn him now! Nikamaru!
Hold your cannon!
I don't know.
Thank you.
I'll never forget about it.
If you want to know what I want,
I'll still believe my life.
I don't think I'm going to die.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to get you.
You can always be the same.
I'm going to die.
I decided I'd never tell anyone about
the things I truly want to keep secret.
After I wrote what type of boy I like
in my notebook back in grade school?
and let everyone find out!
Next time, Evening Festival!
What did you write?
I don't mind.
He does seem like he'd be fast.